Exit Art "Reactions" exhibit collection
Prints & Photographs Division, Library of Congress
- Gordon, Peter
  - [Untitled], 0850; 3047
- Gorewitz, Shalom
  - [Untitled], print; 0851; 234
- Gorman, Deborah Angyo
  - Innocence Catching Despair, collage; 0852; 271
- Gormley, Brian
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0853; 1017; Abstract chaotic images
- Gortchakova, Eugenia
  - [Untitled], 0854; 516; "Its about you"
- Gould, Melissa
  - In Memoriam 2001, 0855; 275; Same image as 276, different size image
- Gould, Melissa
  - In Memoriam, 0856; 276; 2001 same image as 275 different size
- Gouueia, Marcia A.
  - [Untitled], 0857; 144; From Mt. Ida College drawing class
- Gracie, Alison
  - Fester, oil on canvas; 0858; 711
- Grant, Lorenna
  - Veil, fabric; 0860; 1064; Black background with abstract white shape off center and white text
- Grassini, Carlo
  - [Untitled], 0861; 193; "Enter Art the Only World"
- Graupe-Pillard, Grace
  - Scream-9/11/01, 0862; 47; Woman's face seen through double image of man running. Hands cross below her eye in the center.
- Gray, Michael
  - [Untitled], 0863; 554; 6 of 16
- Green Jo-Anne
  - [Untitled], digital photo; 0864; 61; Via mail
- Green, Lorna
  - Power Flowers, 0865; 594
- Greenberg, Theresa
  - The Center of the Universe, 0866; 1637; Abstracted horizontal image title on bottom left
- Gross, C.M.
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0869; 717; Horizontal image of man holding up flag - digital collage
- Gross, C.M.
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0870; 718; Young boy with flag images www.cmgross.com
- Grossman, Joe
  - [Untitled], 0871; 16; Poem via email
- Grzybowski, Peter
  - Stand, digital print (inkjet); 0872; 1373; Image of WTC tower smoking and an American flag and "Made in China" logo in foreground. Text: "United we stand?"
- Guajardo, Michael
  - Giants, 0873; 900; Poem
- Guedel, Kaloust
  - [Untitled], 0874; 1647; Invitation card featuring artists recent paintings titled "help", "war state of mind", "NY", "Hijack", "Give Peace a Chance", "Explosion"
- Guerin, Magalie
  - I can't fucking sleep (self-portrait '01), photograph; 0875; 1044
- Guerreiro, Sandra
  - no name for evolution, digital image; 0876; 777; Text and image
- Gugel, Fernando
  - Proposal: A monument for Healing-not to be built, 0877; 644; Photo of clear towers
- Gulrich, Kathy
  - Hurting, healing - A Compassionate Response to the Events of, paper collage; 0879; 1869; The compassion exercise
- Gustafson, Karin
  - [Untitled], 0880; 1435; Elephants
- Gyeinfoc, Safe
  - [Untitled], 0881; 546; 13 of 16
- Hackemann, Rebecca
  - What goes around, comes around, toned silver gelatin print; 0883; 458
- Hackteri
  - A Sea of Tears Surrounding Our Island, watercolor/paint/pencil; 0885; 957
- Haendel, Karl Frederick
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper, newspaper page; 0886; 317; Untitled (black wave) 2002
- Haggerty, Gerard
  - Early Warning, color xerox; 0887; 1490; Collage of photos of Afghanistan terrain with text "Early Warning" bordering the images
- Haghi, Nina
  - [Untitled], pen and marker on paper; 0888; 842; Line drawing of large man wearing a shirt made of a U.S. flag towering over the burning towers
- Hahn, Hannelore
  - Fingerprints, photograph; 0889; 1070; Photograph of WTC revolving doors bordered by a fingerprint design with text above and below image
- Hahne, Marj
  - Rememberance for September 11, 2001, 0890; 408; "Even a woman..."
- Hahne, Marj
  - A New York Winter, 0891; 409; "Piano, violin..."
- HAI
  - The September 11th Tragedy, 0892; 1651; 1651-1687; "there is absolutely no words..."
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0893; 1652; 1651-1687; "has left me sad..."
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0894; 1653; 1651-1687; "the attack that occurred..."
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0895; 1654; 1651-1687; frontal face
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0896; 1655; 1651-1687; "all people come aboard now"
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0897; 1656; 1651-1687; praying hands
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0898; 1657; 1651-1687; "eye has not seen..."
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0899; 1658; 1651-1687; "made me feel depressed..."
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0900; 1659; 1651-1687; Bin Laden's esp
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0901; 1660; 1651-1687; money
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0902; 1661; 1651-1687; house
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0903; 1662; 1651-1687; "I see my heart..."
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0904; 1663; 1651-1687; "crown jewels..."
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0905; 1664; 1651-1687
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0906; 1665; 1651-1687; "I got scared."
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0907; 1666; 1651-1687; "I wish it never..."
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0908; 1667; 1651-1687; "My heart was very sad..."
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0909; 1668; 1651-1687; "I try to do everything"
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0910; 1669; 1651-1687; "death came..."
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0911; 1670; 1651-1687; star
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0912; 1671; 1651-1687; "I will never forget"
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0913; 1672; 1651-1687; "untouchables"
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0914; 1673; 1651-1687; crying face
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0915; 1674; 1651-1687; plane and guy
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0917; 1677; 1651-1687; missing 1676
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0918; 1678; 1651-1687; love is what...
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0919; 1679; 1651-1687; repent
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0920; 1680; 1651-1687; 9/11/01 made me very sad
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0921; 1681; 1651-1687; shock
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0922; 1682; 1651-1687; upsetting
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0923; 1683; 1651-1687; brrrr
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0924; 1684; 1651-1687; America the beauty
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0925; 1685; 1651-1687; never forget the WTC
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0926; 1686; 1651-1687; yelling people
- HAI
  - [Untitled], 0927; 1687; 1651-1687; forks
- Hall, Tom
  - [Untitled], ink on paper; 0928; 420; Drawing of two bright yellow towers w/black ink and marker on white paper
- Hakola, Marikki
  - [Untitled], 0929; 176; Continuum.3 1 of 3
- Hakola, Marikki
  - [Untitled], 0930; 177; Finland Continuum 2 of 3
- Hakola, Marikki
  - [Untitled], 0931; 178; Continuum.1 3 of 3
- Haley, Nade
  - Brooklyn 2001, 0932; 442; 2/15
- Hall, Jessica
  - I Watch the Sky A Lot, picture (digital print); 0933; 426
- Hall, Marcellus
  - [Untitled], drawings; 0935; 1943; 4 drawings: Union Sq, St. Vincents, etc.
- Haller, Robert A.
  - from the Book: We Too Are Alive: Poems After and Before 9/11, photograph; 0936; 893; Photo of firefighters
- Halpern, John
  - Artists Call, 0937; 1194; "you are the solution..."
- Halsall, Doreen
  - [Untitled], 0938; 470; Twisted shape
- Halsall, Tom
  - [Untitled], 0939; 471; Rumpled paper man
- Hamblen, Martin
  - [Untitled], print; 0940; 776; Red, white, and blue distorted American flag
- Hammer, Barbara
  - Twins, photograph; 0941; 946
- Hamon, Matt
  - [Untitled], gelatin silver print; 0942; 838
- Hancon, John
  - [Untitled], 0943; 626; The Tower
- Handelman, Michelle
  - I Started Smoking, 0944; 2031; Girl smoking, drinking and popping pills
- Handelsman, Jared
  - Wood Piles, photograph; 0946; 1871
- Handspicker, Sara
  - I felt--shocked & angry. USA, united, democracy, equality..., drawing; 0947; 397; age: 12 1/2
- Hanoch, Doron
  - [Untitled], photo; 0948; 609; Man
- Hanron, Jody
  - Target, live oil drawing; 0949; 964
- Happy Smith, Abigail
  - September II II II II II II II T RAUMA, Polaroid; 0950; 1138
- Hardinger, Ruth
  - [Untitled], two digital photos; 0951; 1828; Two digital images one photo the other a watercolor
- Harris, Joshua
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 0952; 1558; Detailed pencil drawing on white paper of man kneeling on carpet and an amorphic creature in foreground
- Harris, Katherine Anne
  - [Untitled], comp print; 0952b; 3272
- Harrsch, Erika
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0953; 695; Hand
- Harse, Debra
  - [Untitled], 0954; 1143; Guy with yankee shirt
- Hartling, Cynthia
  - [Untitled], 0956; 1873; Construction workers
- Hartling, Cynthia
  - [Untitled], 0957; 1874; Street w/squares
- Hartling, Cynthia
  - [Untitled], 0958; 1875; Man w/squiggles over him
- Hartman, Carey
  - Untitled and after thinking on where i stand, poems; 0959; 2179
- Hartman, Carrie
  - [Untitled], colored paper; 0962; 1870; Crying blood
- Hartung, Susan
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0963; 814
- Haskett, Michael
  - Indian summer: September 22, 2002, text and digital image on paper; 0964; 1007; 6 line poem above digital image
- Haskett, Michael
  - Like Lost Children In The Night Tundra, poem; 0965; 2175; My tears fell in slow motion
- Haskett, Mike
  - Sallustus, from The Marriage of Cadmus and Harmony, Roberto, print; 0966; 183
- Hassakis, Greta
  - Media Overload and Scramble, 0967; 418; Part of larger work with same name; drawing of TV set
- Hatch, Sarah
  - [Untitled], 0968; 1049
- Hatchett, David
  - Business As Usual, Text; 0969; 1196
- Hatchett, Lily
  - [Untitled], 0970; 1635; Six photographic images. Top image reflection of towers in building. Bottom image construction workers standing in a dumpster wearing hardhats
- Hauer, Kimberly Frances
  - 9/11/2001 T.F.G., 0971; 1151
- Hauser, Erica
  - [Untitled], copy of original painting, acrylic on canvas; 0972; 686
- Haveson, Cori
  - [Untitled], 0973; 1128; Your lack of curiosity
- Hawkins, Clymenza
  - Ashes of the World, 0974; 1644; Text starting with "I used to work the morning shift at the Borders Bookstore at the World Trade Center." on right side of page. Collage of church and map on left side.
- Hayashi, Sachiko
  - [Untitled], 0975; 2070; Osama
- Haynes, Stuart
  - [Untitled], comp art; 0976b; 3291; Fly, fly Butterfly
- Healy, Angela
  - The Nation's Greatest, 0977; 1152; By Mike Stellmacher-part of pack from Healy
- Healy, Angela
  - The Parking Attendant, 0978; 1153; Part of pack from Healy
- Healy, Angela
  - A Day of Terror, 0979; 1154; By Pat McShane-part of pack from Healy
- Healy, Angela
  - [Untitled], 0980; 1155; Anon.-part of pack from Healy
- Healy, Angela
  - [Untitled], 0981; 1156; Anon.-part of pack from Healy; "we support you"
- Healy, Angela
  - [Untitled], 0982; 1157; Anon.-part of pack from Healy; collage "time heals all"
- Healy, Angela
  - [Untitled], 0983; 1158; Anon.-part of pack from Healy; collage "the US is strong..."
- Healy, Angela
  - [Untitled], 0984; 1159; Anon.-part of pack from Healy; collage US map
- Hecker
  - [Untitled], 0985; 440; Death car freshener
- Heffin, Joel
  - [Untitled], photo with text; 0986; 419
- Heil, Jane
  - [Untitled], text; 0987; 75
- Held, Marion E.
  - [Untitled], 0988; 164; Drawing
- Hellberg, Gustav
  - [Untitled], 0989; 868; Time out
- Hellstrom, Patter
  - Nishi Nippon Bank Ltd., 0990; 664; Part of the series, Target Hear: Calling All Angels
- Henderson, David
  - [Untitled], 0991; 2007; Frost St in Brooklyn
- Hendricks, Jon
  - [Untitled], 0992; 204; Commentary on reactions letter
- Heneberger, Tracy
  - Cloud, collage; 0993; 1512
- Heneller, Elizabeth
  - [Untitled], 0994; 1788; Girl w/WTC eyes
- Henes, Donna
  - A full week after the blasts, there are still immense clouds of smoke coming from lower Manhattan..., picture (digital print); 0995; 99; Artwork & text via mail
- Henry, Alicia
  - [Untitled], 0996; 863; Sad face
- Herder, Jon
  - thanks a lot, color xerox; 0996b; 3265
- Herdlein, Bob
  - A Plotinus Corner, 0997; 3034
- Herman, David
  - [Untitled], photo collage; 0998; 358; Night Elegy
- Herman, Jerry
  - A Vile Vial of Violence, 0999; 140
- Herman, Kate
  - [Untitled], 1000; 14; Poem via email
- Herman, Kate
  - Light Ray, 1001; 3018; Poem via email start with "Sky impossibly bright"
- Herskowitz, Mara
  - [Untitled], 1002; 2228; Washington
- Herskowitz, Mara
  - [Untitled], 1003; 2229; Einstein
- Herskowitz, Mara
  - [Untitled], 1004; 2230; Roses
- Herskowitz, Mara
  - [Untitled], 1005; 2231; Skyline
- Herskowitz, Mara
  - [Untitled], 1006; 2232; Skyline
- Hesh, Linda
  - Safe/Suspect, photograph (digital print); 1007; 2202
- Hester, Katie
  - [Untitled], 1008; 318; Heart drawings
- Hewitt, David
  - [Untitled], comp print; 1008b; 3238
- Hewitt, Laura C.
  - [Untitled], 1009; 168
- Hewlett, Mary-Lou
  - [Untitled], 1010; 434; Coffee cups and cupcakes
- Heydenreich, Ulrike
  - [Untitled], photographs; 1011; 1255; 4 small images of man wrapped in flag arranged in a row vertically
- Hickey, Sean
  - The Birds of Barclay Street, 1012; 874
- Hieber, Lutz
  - Reaktion, 1014; 1200; German text
- High, Linda Oatman
  - Attention: Terrorists, 1015; 2125
- Hildebidle, John J.
  - The Silence, poem; 1017; 2135; I was maybe seven, maybe nine;...
- Hill, Logan
  - [Untitled], 1019; 2268; Hi, I received your letter...
- Hill, Michelle
  - [Untitled], 1020; 1822; I taste with my eyes
- Hilmi, Nabila
  - [Untitled], goro print of original oil painting on paper; 1021; 457
- Hilton, Jim
  - [Untitled], 1022; 3040
- Hinkis, Tali
  - [Untitled], 1023; 1938
- Hinkis, Tali
  - [Untitled], 1024; 1939
- Hiott, Bryon
  - The Latest News from the Front, 1025; 1642; Image of two abstracted figures. One saying "looking for anthrax in quite tedious"
- Hirsch, Steve
  - Leaves In The Margins, 1027; 3042; Second poem "leaves in the margins"
- Hirsch, Steven
  - [Untitled], 1028; 2162
- Hisagima, Sachiko
  - The Thinker, 1029; 1503; 6W2H
- Hitchcock, John
  - CRUSADE/WANTED, digital print; 1030; 1880; Crusade/soldier
- Hitchcock, John
  - CRUSADE/WANTED, digital print; 1031; 1881; Wanted/cowboy
- Hitchcock, John
  - CRUSADE/WANTED, digital print; 1032; 1882; Crusade, soldier w/raised gun
- Hitchcock, John
  - CRUSADE/WANTED, digital print; 1033; 1883; Wanted, indian
- Hoag, Linda Anne
  - Trump, poem; 1034; 2218
- Hoberman, Jim
  - [Untitled], 1035; 883
- Hodgkin, Carter
  - Prayer for My Block--Chambers Street, collage; 1036; 861; Street
- Hoefle, Krista
  - [Untitled], 1037; 848; Text towers
- Hoffberg, Judith A.
  - [Untitled], 1039; 2036; Missing World Financial Capital
- Hoffman, Eileen
  - [Untitled], 1040; 689
- Hollings, Paula
  - [Untitled], 1041; 2289; The essence of life has NOT...
- Holloway, Anne Audley
  - Voices from the Sky 9/11, print; 1042; 934; Squares NYC
- Holly, Bud
  - Heat Stroke, 1043; 671; Rantings in childlike scrawl
- Holman, Bob
  - [Untitled], 1045; 2118
- Holman, George R.
  - New Twin Towers Concept, 1046; 633
- Holsinger, Jayne
  - [Untitled], 1047; 743; Image of a Continental Airlines airplane
- Hongtu, Zhang
  - "On the wall", digital image; 1048; 1829; Mona Lisa image with missing posters
- Hood, Mary
  - [Untitled], 1049; 315; Idea/actual..."
- Hoop
  - If I Could Turn Back Time, 1050; 688; Clock van man
- Hoovler, William
  - Wais-R Block, 1051; 443
- Hopper, Phil
  - [Untitled], 1052; 416; Journal entry
- Hoskinson
  - [Untitled], 1053; 1236; "you will surely..." poem
- House, Melissa
  - [Untitled], 1054; 49; Journal entry via email
- Houston, Jessica Perl
  - [Untitled], 1055; 248; Bees and tub
- Hoveyda, Niloufar
  - September 11, 1056; 1085; Two abstract figures on right, one in middleground and one in the background
- Hoveyda, Niloufar
  - September 11, 1057; 1084; Screaming woman clutching child in foreground, man running in middleground, falling towers against a smoke filled sky in background
- Hoveyda, Niloufar
  - September 11, 1058; 1083; Image of twin towers in a dark smokey sky with a thick uneven black border
- Howard, Rachel
  - [Untitled], 1059; 1561; Abstract amorphic image with dark background
- Howie, Philip
  - [Untitled], 1060; 1161; Reclining woman
- Hrab, Roman M.
  - View of the World Financial Center from Riverview Park, Jersey, digital image; 1061; 1378; Digital photo; dark undefined mass coming up from bottom of page
- Hsu, Tonia K.
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 1062; 1413; Abstract design with a circle in center
- Huang, Shih-Chieh
  - [Untitled], 1063; 1248; Reactions with flag overlay
- Huerta, Benito
  - Night Between Frontiers, pencil; 1064; 859
- Huffman, Carlos M.
  - one world, copy of drawing; 1064b; 3234
- Humphrey, Nene
  - [Untitled], 1065; 143; Account, "Sunday, to the World Trade Center..."
- Humphrey, Sheryl
  - detail of Melusina, 1066; 710; Woman half light.dark
- Hung, Su-Li
  - Burning the Incense #1, collage; 1067; 1582
- Hung, Su-Li
  - Burning the Incense #2, collage; 1068; 1583
- Hung, Su-Li
  - Burning the Incense #3, collage; 1069; 1584
- Hung Su-Li
  - Burning the Incense #4, collage; 1070; 1585
- Hung, Su-Li
  - Burning the Incense #5, collage; 1071; 1586
- Hunt, Lenore
  - [Untitled], photograph; 1072; 932; Girl in driveway
- Hunter, Christpher Douglas
  - Poem for New York, 1073; 3006
- Huschle, Charles
  - Capturing The Dog, poem; 1075; 2264; All my attempts to capture the day...
- Huttner, Per
  - [Untitled], 1077; 3004
- Huynh, Kim
  - American Stain, mixed media; 1078; 2093; White hand in center w/text against a dark background
- Hyde, Jenny
  - Mend, 1079; 571; Sewn
- Iba, Akiko
  - [Untitled], wax paper stuck to it; 1081; 1751
- Ibar, Manech
  - [Untitled], poem and image; 1081b; 3275
- Ibrahim, Noor Effendy
  - Memorial for Loss, digital image; 1082; 2074; Text
- Ivanoska, Kristina
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1085; 1381; Line drawing of connected boards located at bottom of white page
- Irizarry, Linda
  - [Untitled], 1086; 232; 1 of 2 drawings
- Irizarry, Linda
  - [Untitled], 1087; 233; 2 of 2 drawings
- Irving, Lauren
  - [Untitled], laser print of painting; 1088; 882
- Isasi, Carmen
  - [Untitled], 1089; 3045; Poem
- Mycklebust, Scotto Iverson
  - Study for Summer 11 painting, laser print and gouache on strathmore paper.; 1090; 692; Globs
- Ivy, Candice
  - [Untitled], 1091; 1551; Flowers and chinese calligraphy
- Izolde
  - [Untitled], comp art; 1091b; 3284
- Jaci, Marilia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 1092; 1129; Boxes with holes
- Jackson, Edward
  - [Untitled], 1093; 422
- Jacobson, Jerry
  - [Untitled], 1094; 1046
- Jacoby, Susan G.
  - [Untitled], 1095; 310; Hand
- Jaffe, Lance
  - [Untitled], text; 1095b; 3063; The day the earth shook the world
- Jaffe, Lance
  - [Untitled], text; 1095c; 3064; The Aftermath
- Jaffe, Lance
  - [Untitled], text; 1095d; 3065; World trade
- Jaffe, Lance
  - [Untitled], text; 1095e; 3066; World trade
- Jensen, Diana
  - Missing, watercolor; 1096; 587; Watercolor of faces
- Jack, Jane
  - [Untitled], 1097; 450; "Each moment, only once"
- Jalali, Farhang
  - [Untitled], print; 1098; 179; "Let's Cry Out in Peace"
- Jannone, John A.
  - [Untitled], 1099; 892
- Janto, Phyllis
  - [Untitled], 1100; 1185; "The coast of Lesvos..."
- Jappinen, Jouni Johannes
  - Join in a Ring Around, black and white drawing; 1101; 1937
- Jaquis, Michele
  - [Untitled], 1102; 767; 9.25.01 I'm sorry but I...
- Jaquis, Michele
  - [Untitled], 1103; 768; "9.26.01 for the past few days..."
- Jaxxa, James
  - You're a Very Bad Boy, marker, colored pencil, acrylic, nail enamel, and glitter on paper board; 1104; 869
- Jeanne Ave
  - Thin Children Beneath September Sun, poem; 1105; 2172
- Jeanne-Claude, Christo and
  - [Untitled], Text; 1106; 69
- Jeehyun, Kim Sofie
  - [Untitled], collage; 1107; 935; Triangles
- Jenks, Debra
  - [Untitled], 1108; 1141; Newsstand
- Jezek, Tom
  - Elegy No. 2, 1109; 1505; WTC towers
- Jo, Sook Jin
  - [Untitled], 1110; 1042
- Jo/Suejin
  - [Untitled], 1111; 311; Crosses made of photos
- Johnson, Amy
  - [Untitled], 1112; 225; Hands
- Johnson, Andrew
  - [Untitled], 1112b; 3220
- Johnson, Liz
  - September 12, 2001, new vocabulary ground zero, the pile, suicide hijackers, missing..., manuscript (digital print); 1113; 289
- Johnson, Nikki
  - Toy Gun, photo with text; 1115; 807; Image of man holding gun pointed at viewer
- Jones, Brian
  - We All Bleed the Same, painting; 1116; 881
- Jones, Dr. Cameron L.
  - Wrist Camera Dice Echoes, 3D photographic digital art on paper; 1117; 1608; 3D collaged images
- Jones, Jupiter
  - Confusion, text; 1118; 3299
- Jurinek, Jerilyn
  - Scapegoat Interval, 1119; 622; Poem w/red image
- Joseph, Rene
  - [Untitled], 1120; 89; Artwork
- Joshua
  - [Untitled], 1121; 547; 12 of 16
- Joy, Joseph
  - American Flag, 1122; 235; G"
- Joyner, Phyllis
  - [Untitled], 1124; 1246; Nail salon phone page
- Jungle, Tadeu
  - Everything is possible (to be lost), 1125; 96; 1 of 2 artwork www.playgod.cjb.net
- Jungle, Tadeu
  - Playgod, 1126; 97; 2 of 2 Title for 2 - Series of Stickers www.playgod.cjb.net
- K., Tania
  - [Untitled], 1127; 223; "More collaboration is happening now"
- Kaden, Chelsea
  - [Untitled], 1128; 209; Part of group from students of the Hudson School, "Looking Out a Window"
- Kadichevski, Liliana
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1129; 3213; "out of mind" written across three photos of a hand in a pink circle
- Kagan, David B.
  - [Untitled], 1130; 1774; JP morgan
- Kahane, Lisa
  - Gone, photograph; 1131; 993; Photograph of lower east side skyline with twin towers in the background
- Kalas, Leon Nicholas
  - Attack on America and Reaction, oil on canvas 20" x 24" and poem; 1132; 783; Copy of painting with poem
- Kane, Dana
  - [Untitled], digital image; 1133; 879; Teapots
- Kanemaru, Tomomi Maru
  - Love is the World. Love is People, 1134; 1238; World map w/hearts
- Kang, Joo Hyun
  - [Untitled], pencil on paper; 1135; 808; Drawing
- Kang, Joo Hyun
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 1136; 809
- Kanidinc, Elena Ruano
  - Memorial, 1137; 1855; Ashes to ashes
- Kanter, Lynne P.
  - [Untitled], digital image with text; 1138; 1072; Photo of tower taken in 1974, digitally added text and color
- Kaplan, Casey
  - Deigens monster for en orduing (the daily pattern for an order), drawing on paper; 1139; 763; Drawing of a figure with curved lines flowing around
- Karen Lillis Elsa LiDonni
  - Flag City, USA, 1140; 3029; Conversation text via email
- Karen Lillis Elsa LiDonni
  - Flag City, USA, 1141; 3030; Conversation text via email
- Courtney, Matthew
  - [Untitled], marker on newspaper; 1141b; 3222; Bald image on newspaper
- Karlin, Susan
  - [Untitled], drawing; 1142; 613; Sun, landscape
- Karp, Barrie
  - tears, 9/17, 2001, laser photocopy of original Phoenician paper and acid free ink; 1143; 249
- Kashia, Tami
  - To the Workers of Windows on the World, 1144; 1844; Repeated "to the workers..."
- Kashia, Tami
  - To the Workers of Windows on the World, 1145; 1845; The workers at windows on the world came from...
- Kate Schaffer & Sherry Mayo
  - Requiem for the Consciousness Industry, color digital photos; 1146; 701; Photo of bubble people; 1 of 3
- Kate Schaffer & Sherry Mayo
  - Requiem for the Consciousness Industry, color digital photos; 1147; 702; Text to accompany bubble people; 2 of 3
- Kate Schaffer & Sherry Mayo
  - Requiem for the Consciousness Industry, color digital photos; 1148; 703; Text to accompany bubble people; 2 of 3
- Katomski, Kate
  - Union Square Memorial, 1149; 1219; Papers
- Katz, Jessica
  - [Untitled], 1150; 1842; "along w/the appearance..."
- Katz, Marie Christine
  - [Untitled], sketch; 1151; 1199; Manh streets
- Katzman, Don
  - 9/11/01, 1153; 1820; Poem
- Kaufmann, Jesse
  - [Untitled], 1154; 638
- Kassof-Isaac,Rhoda
  - Bereavement, photo; 1155; 1313
- Kearns, Jerry
  - The Elvis Scenario, 1157; 1334; Text and elvis on bike
- Keever, Kim
  - [Untitled], 1158; 709; Branches
- Keil, Renee
  - Digest, oil on acetate and newspaper; 1159; 1364; Dark abstract image
- Keith, Stephaine
  - [Untitled], 1160; 696; Camo couple
- Kelleher, Betsy
  - [Untitled], 1161; 1625
- Kellner, Tatana
  - God Bless America, photography; 1162; 1598; Multiple photos of signs
- Kemmerer, John
  - Under The Haystack Fast Asleep, 1163; 3037
- Kemmerer, John
  - On the Wing, poem; 1164; 3038
- Kemp Haynes, Kathleen
  - [Untitled], 1165; 8; Poem via email
- Kendall, Brad
  - [Untitled], 1166; 3069; Image of angel-like figure sitting on a cinder-block with a halo around its head
- Kendall, Daren
  - 9.11.2001, digital image; 1167; 1863
- Kennedy, Kendal
  - Without My Security Blanket, 1168; 287; "From Serious Toys Series photocollage"
- Kephart, Robert
  - [Untitled], map; 1169; 436; Of U.S.
- Kereszki, Lisa
  - [Untitled], 1170; 1056; No reentry
- Kerekes, Laszlo
  - Life is very close to death, color print; 1170b; 3223
- Kesler, Shields, Anne